You have almost - how many gates?
So you don't need to be on the queue, on the line.
They are many gates.
You can use any entrance.
Okay!
How many gates? One, two, here, four.
You see? Come on! Can you see?
Can you see?
Do you see? He has not entered.
See what is happening.
Even before getting to the altar - see what is happening.
Camera, capture it from there. Can you ask this guy to leave the place?..
Receiving Deliverance On The SCOAN Altar
Okay, take care, please!
When you are going out, there is an entrance here.
Receiving Deliverance On The SCOAN Altar
Leading to the altar.
When you finish at the altar, you can go out through any of the six gates we have.
Receiving Deliverance On The SCOAN Altar
International Visitors On The SCOAN Altar
See what is happening.
Receiving Deliverance On The SCOAN Altar
...Right now, under the influence of the Holy Spirit, the evil spirits in people are manifesting.
What is happening - you can see a woman vomiting and the other woman manifesting.
It happens when people step onto the Synagogue Altar.
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
On The SCOAN Altar
Receiving Deliverance On The SCOAN Altar
Watch the screen, you can see people vomiting out poisonous substances from their system.
By stepping onto the altar, you can see the Lord, God Almighty has taken over their situations, right now.
All that they have taken in their dream and from the table of the enemies
is what the Spirit of God is flushing out right now. Watch the screen.
As you're praying, look at what is happening on the screen. This will help your faith.
Receiving Deliverance On The SCOAN Altar
Vomiting Blood And Poisonous Substances On The SCOAN Altar
What have you done to her?
Destruction, poverty.
Why is she the only one who is married in the family? I will destroy her. She is mine.
Receiving Deliverance on the SCOAN altar
More people are vomiting as they step onto the Synagogue Altar.
You can see what that woman has vomited - poisonous substances from her system.
Vomiting Poisonous Substances On The SCOAN Altar
What did you do to him?
I stopped everything.
What have you done to his carrier?
No carrier.
No carrier. His marriage, his life, his family?
I tied everybody.
How did you enter this body?
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
On The SCOAN Altar
Watch your screen!
More and more people are vomiting. You can see blood in what that woman is vomiting out
to show that it is her problem that has been uprooted, right now, deep down from her system.
Whatever is in the system, there is no hiding place for affliction - here, at the arena of liberty.
Continue to watch your screen.
Vomiting Blood And Poisonous Susbtances On The SCOAN Altar
Thank you, Jesus, I am free. Thank you Jesus, my family is free.
Receiving Deliverance
On The SCOAN Altar
The woman is still vomiting out poisonous substances from her system.
And the other man too, immediately, after stepping onto the Synagogue Altar
is also vomiting strange objects, as we can see right there.
The Spirit of God is uprooting it from the source what satan has planted in their lives.
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
On The SCOAN Altar
What have you done to her? What have you done to her carrier?
I have destroyed her.
Her marriage?
I have destroyed everything. Don't deliver her! Leave her for me.
Who are you?
Spiritual husband.
How did you enter her?
I am from her mother's side.
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
On The SCOAN Altar
Hear the demons confessing already.
The fire of God Almighty is consuming them and exposing them.
We can see what that woman is vomiting out -
more blood substances, that ia a poison in her system
is what she is vomiting out right now.
Thank you, Jesus, I am free, my family is free.
Instant testimony
following instant healing right there, on the altar.
Whatever is your challenge...
Thank you. I am free, my family is free. Thank you, Jesus.
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
On The SCOAN Altar
She will not graduate. She wants to finish her master's, she will not graduate. Leave me alone, she will not finish.
"T.B. Joshua" all the time. "Emmanuel TV". Praying with Emmanuel TV.
Receiving Deliverance On The SCOAN Altar
There's another woman there. As soon as she stepped onto the altar, you can see what she is vomiting out.
And the man struggling there - something is about to come out.
I am a big snake! I came from the sea. No one will destroy me, no one. I destroy everyone in the family.
How did you enter her body?
I entered through dream.
Vomiting Poisonous Substances On The SCOAN Altar
What have you done to her? How many are you in this body? Speak out!
As she stepped onto the altar...
I destroy her.
Who are you in this body?
What have you done to her family, marriage?
Her marriage is destroyed.
How did you enter this body?
I entered her through her father.
You can hear the demon confessing. Satan comes to kill, to steal and to destroy.
Eating in the dream.
Who are you?
Poisonous, I want to kill her.
How did you enter her?
Through dreams.
Watch your screen and see what they are vomiting out.
Those are strange substances from their system, a mixture of blood and other colorful substances.
That's the poison from their system that they still vomiting out right there.
Don't forget that as you climb onto the altar to sanctify yourself.
I am free. Thank you, Jesus.
Thank you, Jesus! I am free, I am delivered. My family is delivered.
After praying at the round top of the altar, we climb up this way.
Thank you, Jesus. I am free.
Vomiting Poisonous Substances On The SCOAN Altar
Thank you, Jesus. I am free, my family is delivered. Thank you.
Thank you, you can see what God has in store for you.
I say, you can see what God has in store for you.
That is to tell you that this coming year, you as a person - glory, glory.
Please, don't waste time here,
just go snappy and pick whatever you want to pick what God had arranged for you.
So that we can arrange ourselves back to the mountain.
We are still going to the mountain.
Vomiting Poisonous Substances On The SCOAN Altar
Please, I want you to be in that place for the new year.
So when everyone is shouting "Happy New Year!", you'll be there under the trees, in the presence of God.
When you leave here,
please go and get your pillow or whatever you want to have with you to the mountain
because you are not going back to your room or to the other side.
YOU'RE WATCHING FROM THE SYNAGOGUE CHURCH OF ALL NATIONS
He refused to serve me. This boy is so stubborn.
He's so stubborn.
He doesn't want to serve me. He doesn't want. I forced him in different ways, he refuses.
He says "no", he will never serve me. He is even making jokes of me.
He says: "Satan, I will never serve you, no matter what you do. I will never serve you."
He is proud. He said he would never serve me.
Who are you in this body?
This boy is very stubborn. I'm the idol from his father's house.
I destroy him. I stop him not to move forward
because this boy is great. He's greater than all his brothers.
If I leave him, nobody will see him back in his village.
I destroy him.
How did you enter him? Speak out!
I entered him through the idol in their family.
Receiving Deliverance On The SCOAN Altar
What have you done to her marriage?
Nothing. She will never, never, never get married in her life.
Why?
I don't know.
Receiving Deliverance On The SCOAN Altar
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits On The SCOAN Altar
Vomiting Poisonous Substances On the SCOAN Altar
Watch your screen and see what that man is vomiting out -
blood substance, whitish substance, yellowish substance -
different poisonous substances.
Vomiting Poisonous Substances On the SCOAN Altar
Thank you, Jesus. It is a new dawn.
THE SCOAN LIVING WATER
Testimony of the instant deliverance right there at the SCOAN Altar.
More and more people, as they step onto the Synagogue Altar are vomiting out
what satan has planted in their system that is destroying their organs.
That is what the Spirit of God is uprooting out of them right now.
Vomiting Poisonous Substances on The SCOAN Altar
The presence of God.
Receiving Deliverance On The SCOAN Altar
Who are you? Who are you in this body?
Family altar.
How did you destroy her?
Sickness, diabetics.
Who is this man to you?
Who?
You can hear the voice of demons.
She is my wife and our children.
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits On The SCOAN Altar
Demons are agents of destruction.
She rules the house, she is too stubborn and keeps a lot of grudges.
She is easily offended and does not let go things easily.
How did you entered her body?
Spirit of anger.
Who gave her that spirit?
Me, the husband.
How did you enter her?
Through dream.
Deliverance is the answer, after the demon has confessed, now is time to leave.
Same on the altar where the demon began to manifest,
there the demon leaves the body and now the victim is set free.
Watch your screen and see what people are still vomiting out.
Thank you, Jesus. I'm free.
Thank you for saving my family.
Thank you, Lord! Thank you, Jesus for delivering this for family.
Vomiting Poisonous Substances On The SCOAN Altar
The SCOAN Living Water
The SCOAN Altar
Anything that satan has planted in the lives of the people,
there is no hiding place right now for any affliction
because the presence of God at the altar is so powerful
to scan through the system and expose and also to flush out whatever is not of God.
Watch the screen and you can see blood and some yellowish substance that woman is vomiting out.
Many people, even before stepping into the altar, the Spirit of God catches up with their problems
and delivers them and heals them. Watch your screen.
Vomiting Blood And Poisonous Substances On The SCOAN Altar
You can see what that woman vomited out of her system.
That is what satan has planted in her life,
what she has eaten from the table of the adversary is what the Spirit of God is uprooting from the source...
...more forms of infirmities.
People are still going onto the altar as instructed by the man of God
that you go to the round altar and pray, and go to the top part of the altar and pray before you go
to the lower part of the altar where you collect the living water as the blessing that the Lord has for us today.
Vomiting Poisonous Substances On The SCOAN Altar
Vomiting Blood And Poisonous Substances On The SCOAN Altar
Continue to watch your screen. Demons are still manifesting.
Remember, demons are responsible for all the agonies, pains and shameful acts in the lives of the people.
Now they have no choice than to leave
because the man of God says the grace that has been given to visit the altar is
because God Almighty wants to usher us into the new year, the coming year in glory.
Leave me alone.
Who are you in this body? Speak out, in Jesus' name!
What have you done to her, to her family, to her marriage?
How did you enter her?
Many! I am the grandfather, I am the grandmother.
What have you done to her marriage, carrier and family?
I destroyed her. She will never progress in whatever she is doing.
Receiving Deliverance On SCOAN Altar
I am a strong man. Family idol. I destroyed everything about them.
I finished them.
Receiving Deliverance On SCOAN Altar
Many! I am the grandfather, I am the grandmother.
Who else are you?
I am spiritual husband, limitation.
What have you done to her marriage, carrier and family?
She will never go anywhere.
How did you enter her?
Through masturbation.
Receiving Deliverance On SCOAN Altar
I am a strong man. Family idol. I destroyed everything about them.
I finished them.
How did you enter her body?
Through her grandparents.
Receiving Deliverance On SCOAN Altar
Idol. It is me!
Thank you, Jesus. I am delivered.
Set Free In Jesus' Name
YOU'ARE WATCHING FROM THE SYNAGOGUE CHURCH OF ALL NATIONS LAGOS NIGERIA
Receiving Deliverance On The SCOAN Altar
What have you done to her marriage, her carrier, her family?
How many are you in this body?
You said you are who?
What have you done to the family?
Receiving Deliverance On The SCOAN Altar
You did what? Speak out!
What have you done to her marriage, her carrier, her family?
Speak out! Who are you? You did what? Speak!
What have you done to her career, her family?
How did you destroy her? Speak!
How many are you in this body?
You said you are who?
Idol.
What have you done to her?
I destroy her neck. I make her to have a neck operation.
What have you done to the family?
I tied them.
What have you done to her marriage?
No children. She can't conceive.
conceive.
Vomiting Poisonous Substances On The SCOAN Altar
I am one they serve. I own the community. That family is blessed.
So I cannot let anyone destroy me because she wants to come and ruin the community. But no way.
I have destroyed her. Every time she writes an exam, I will not let her pass. Her father served me.
Death.
What have you done to her, her family, carrier, marriage?
How many of you are in this body? Speak out, in Jesus' name.
What have you done to her, her family, her marriage?
I am killing the family, one by one. I am killing everything.
How did you enter her?
Through food.
Receiving Deliverance On The SCOAN Altar
International Visitors Receiving The Living Water On The SCOAN Altar
Who else are you in this body?
I am a spiritual husband.
What have you done to her?
Disappointment, no marriage, no peace. I frustrate her in everything she does.
Watch the screen and see what is happening, as you are waiting to step onto the altar.
Thank you, Jesus for setting me free.
Receiving Deliverance On The SCOAN Altar
Who are you?
Who is number three?
How did you enter her?
Receiving Deliverance On The SCOAN Altar
Who are you?
How many are you in this body? Speak out!
Thank you, Jesus. Thank you, Jesus. I am free.
Why do you want to destroy her?
Spirit of murmur.
Who is number two?
Who are you in this body? Speak out!
Who is number three?
I am her uncle. I am rich. I want to kill her because she wants to deliver the family.
She is destroying me. She is destroying my business.
How did you enter her?
Through her clothes when she went for a trip with my kids.
Every source of torment, of affliction, of sorrow, of hardship in the life of the people
You can see what that woman is vomiting out of her system. That is what has contaminated her system
Why do you want to destroy her?
and destroying her organs. That is what the Spirit of God is taking out of her now.
Vomiting Poisonous Substances On The SCOAN Altar
Who are you in this body? Speak out!
I'll kill her. I've given her a lot of sicknesses.
I gave her cancer, high cholesterol.
I want her to be in the wheelchair. She came in a wheelchair.
As family, I gave her son low sperm count. He cannot impregnate a woman.
I have given her daughter high blood pressure.
She is destroying me. She is destroying my business.
I said, you cannot save her. I have entered from the beginning.
I prevent her to get any promotion or any job. She will just be at the same position until she dies.
See what that woman is vomiting.
Through her clothes when she went for a trip with my kids.
Every source of torment, of affliction, of sorrow, of hardship in the life of the people
are being exposed as they step onto the SCOAN Altar.
Who are you? Who are you, in Jesus' name? Speak out! How many powers do you have? How did you get in this body?
Vomiting Poisonous Substances On The SCOAN Altar
You said what? How many power do you have? Where are those powers located? Who are you? Speak out!
I am powerful!
Vomiting Blood and Poisonous Substances On the SCOAN Altar
The SCOAN Altar
I make her suffer and cry a lot.
I gave her cancer, high cholesterol.
I want her to be in the wheelchair. She came in a wheelchair.
What have you done to her?
I destroyed her. No destiny.
Receiving Deliverance On The SCOAN Altar
I said, you cannot save her. I have entered from the beginning.
And right here, at this hour, whatever demon has destroyed in your life,
See what that woman is vomiting.
Vomiting out poisonous substances planted by demons and their agents in the life of this woman.
Can you see the color.
So open your heart as you're going to the altar and allow God Almighty to work in your situation.
With God all things are possible.
vomited as terrible poisonous substance
You said what? How many power do you have? Where are those powers located? Who are you? Speak out!
As he stepped onto the altar, the Spirit of God began to flush out everything that satan has planted in his life.
everything that satan has planted
International Visitors Receiving Deliverance On the SCOAN Altar
I destroy.
People who are still stepping onto the Synagogue altar and
the Lord, God Almighty is doing what He has promised to do.
The presence of His angels and His power there is uprooting from the source
How did you get into her?
as many of them have been exposed when the demons spoke out,
and those that the sickness has destroyed their organs are also been set free,
and those poisonous substances are flushed out of their systems so that they can be free.
What have you done to her?
This is what satan has planted that is tormenting her day and night.
She has tried all she could to find solution - all to no avail. But today the Lord is making the way,
where there's no way in her life and flushing out what satan has planted in her life.
You hear from the demon, whatever challenges,
Thank you, Jesus, I am free.
And right here, at this hour, whatever demon has destroyed in your life,
will be restored after they are cast out of your life.
So open your heart as you're going to the altar and allow God Almighty to work in your situation.
With God all things are possible.
You can see the lady has been delivered and watch your screen
and see what this person has vomited as terrible poisonous substance right now.
As he stepped onto the altar, the Spirit of God began to flush out everything that satan has planted in his life.
Thank you, Jesus. I'm free.
International Visitors Receiving Deliverance On the SCOAN Altar
Vomiting Poisonous Substances On The SCOAN Altar
People who are still stepping onto the Synagogue altar and
the Lord, God Almighty is doing what He has promised to do.
The presence of His angels and His power there is uprooting from the source
of what satan has planted in the life of people putting an end to the demonic activities in the life of the people,
as many of them have been exposed when the demons spoke out,
and those that the sickness has destroyed their organs are also been set free,
and those poisonous substances are flushed out of their systems so that they can be free.
You can see what that woman is vomiting out of her system.
This is what satan has planted that is tormenting her day and night.
She has tried all she could to find solution - all to no avail. But today the Lord is making the way,
where there's no way in her life and flushing out what satan has planted in her life.
International Visitors Receiving Deliverance On the SCOAN Altar
Thank you, Jesus, I am free.
Watch the screen, as you are praying on the altar,
take your time to look around and see what the angels of God are doing all around you.
Many that are demon-possessed,
have been exposed and those that have been tormented by sicknesses and diseases
have been set free, as they vomited out different poisonous substances.
So with an open heart,
go to the round altar, to the topmost part of the altar and pray, then go where you will get the living water.
The man of God says these are blessings that the Lord want to give to us to usher us into the year 2019.
It's a special blessing, you can see the evidence all around you as they are there at the altar praying,
there are more people around you are vomiting out different poisonous substances
that satan has planted in their life.
They are flushing out all those things that has contaminated their system and destroyed their organs,
so that they can be free.
International Visitors Receiving Deliverance On the SCOAN Altar
There's no longer hiding place for the demons.
Their activities in the life of the people is what the Spirit of God wants to put an end to,
as they step onto the Synagogue altar after tormenting these people for so long.
They have put hardship and affliction into their life.
Right now, the Spirit of God is putting an end to the work of satan in the life of the people fulfilling the promise.
He promised that he will serve his ancestors. That is why I have destroyed him from his birth.
Who are you in this body? Speak out!
Don't kill me.
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits On The SCOAN Altar
No job.
What have you done to her marriage?
Two miscarriages.
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits On The SCOAN Altar
The Spirit of God is all knowing.
She has sleepless nights.
How did you enter her body?
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits On The SCOAN Altar
The Spirit of God exposes the demonic activities in the life of the people on the same altar
they are delivered from all these works of satan and set free for the salvation of their souls.
You can see another woman vomiting out poisonous substances deposited in her system.
International Visitors Receiving Deliverance On The SCOAN Altar
Viewers all over the world, stay connected in faith, as you watch live on Emmanuel TV
international visitors receiving their deliverance as they follow the instruction
from the man of God Prophet T.B. Joshua to sanctify their hearts as they climb the altar of God
and pray with all their hearts, as they prepare to enter into the new year 2019.
Wherever you are, distance is not a barrier. You too can receive your deliverance,
your healing, your blessing, as you connect by faith.
YOU ARE WATCHING FROM THE SYNAGOGUE CHURCH OF ALL NATIONS LAGOS NIGERIA
The SCOAN Altar
International Visitors Praying On The SCOAN Altar
Vomiting Poisonous Substances On The SCOAN Altar
There is another woman there still vomiting out all what satan has planted in her life.
You can see her fingers shaking.
The presence of the power of God is uprooting from the source whatever satan must have planted in her life
that is tormenting and afflicting her, so that she can be free and walk in Liberty into the year 2019.
As a man of God has said, you've got a glory for us as we open our heart
and supplicate before the Lord, pray unto Him for His blessing and His grace.
You can see what the power of God is doing in the life of the people as they step onto the Synagogue altar.
Receiving Deliverance On The SCOAN Altar
YOU ARE WATCHING FROM THE SYNAGOGUE CHURCH OF ALL NATIONS LAGOS NIGERIA
THANK YOU FOR WATCHING
All over the world, there is something moving South, it is busy spreading East and West and it is marching.
It is bringing the Gospel of Jesus Christ to the four corners of the earth.
This is Emmanuel TV
God with us
Beauty Of Life
The beauty of life does not depend on how happy you are
but on how happy others can be because of you.
How many lives have you touched?
Somebody needs something you possess.
It maybe you love, your smile - genuine one.
It may be your money, your strength, your time.
Most of us here - we always wait until people are crying for help before we can help.
Such love cannot attract God's attention.
And now, these three remain: faith, hope and love. But the greatest of these is love.
Let someone say: "Let love lead".
Yes, if love is the greatest, you should let it lead you every where, day by day.
Love.
Beauty Of Life
It's not what you give that attracts God's attention,
it's not millions you are giving.
It's not all your possession you give but the manner and the way you give them attracts God's attention.
Salvation means contentment, to be content.
Are you content?
Ask Zacchaeus in Luke 19, verse 9.
Zacchaeus will tell you that when he decided to give...
RV: Pavel Tatyana Zheleznyakov 22/04/2019